A Guide to the Policy Office: General Assembly Legislation of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1993.
Library of Virginia
- General Assembly Legislation, 1992.
  - House of Delegates Bills, 1992.
    - HB 569 (92) Boundary between Virginia and West Virginia, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - HB 572 (92) Public hearing for garbage and refuse collection by water and sewer authorities, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - HB 574 (92) Bingo games, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - HB 577 (92) Veterinary professionals - Immunity for civil liability, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - HB 578 (92) Forest wardens - Legal fees and expenses, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - HB 580 (92) Low-income housing credit, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - HB 581 (92) Virginia individual income taxes, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - HB 582 (92) Excess Cost Recovery Program, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - HB 583 (92) Computation of Virginia taxable income, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - HB 585 (92) Workers' Compensation Act - Death benefits, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - HB 586 (92) Special absentee ballots for statewide elections for overseas voters, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - HB 590 (92) Augmented estate, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - HB 591 (92) Profits from crime, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - HB 596 (92) Rental location agents, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - HB 597 (92) Fees for service of process, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - HB 619 (92) Payment of local taxes, fees and charges by credit card, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - HB 623 (92) Ballots, poll books and election materials - Electronic, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - HB 625 (92) Service of process, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - HB 626 (92) Dept. of Youth and Family Services - Placement of children in custody, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - HB 628 (92) Local fire marshals, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - HB 629 (92) Toy-related deaths and injuries, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - HB 630 (92) Location of jail facilities, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - HB 634 (92) Freedom of Information Act, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - HB 635 (92) Consumer Protection Act - Layaways, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - HB 641 (92) Dept. of Waste Management, Director of - Vacancies, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - HB 645 (92) Pesticide Control Board, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - HB 646 (92) Contracts for sale of residential property, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - HB 647 (92) Owners title insurance, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - HB 648 (92) Contractors - Licensure of owner-developers, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - HB 649 (92) Juvenile courts - Intakes, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - HB 656 (92) Educational programs, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - HB 658 (92) House of Delegates district line and adjustments enacted in 1991, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - HB 660 (92) Insurance contracts - Modified guaranteed lif and annuity, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - HB 661 (92) Investment advisor representatives and broker-dealer agents, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - HB 662 (92) State Corporation Commission - Investment advisors and representative, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - HB 663 (92) Prime Quality commercial paper - Investment of Commonwealth funds, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - HB 664 (92) Virginia State Lottery, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - HB 665 (92) Illegal gambling - Purchase/sale of out of state lottery tickets, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - HB 666 (92) State Lottery Dept., 1992. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - HB 667 (92) Certificates of need, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - HB 668 (92) Child visitation, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - HB 669 (92)- Uniforms in public schools, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - HB 672 (92) Virginia Real Estate Transaction Recovery Fund, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - HB 673 (92) Motor vehicle code, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - HB 674 (92) Motor vehicle dealers, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - HB 675 (92) Motor vehicle dealers, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - HB 676 (92) Motor vehicle dealers - Factory repurchase, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - HB 677 (92) Commissioner, Dept. of Motor Vehicles and Motor Vehicles Dealer's Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - HB 678 (92) Motor vehicle dealers - Dealerships, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - HB 679 (92) Removal of trash and garbage, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - HB 680 (92) Defaults on payments, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - HB 681 (92) Removal of unsafe buildings, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - HB 684 (92) Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - HB 686 (92) Required notice of optimal insurance coverage available for motor vehicles, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - HB 687 (92) Regional jail boards, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - HB 688 (92) Virginia Retirement System - Health insurance for retired members, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - HB 690 (92) Property Owners' Association Act, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - HB 699 (92) Virginia Apprenticeship Council, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - HB 700 (92) Municipalities furnishing gas service, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - HB 702 (92) Appurtenances, relocation of easements, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - HB 703 (92) Laboratory Services Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - HB 704 (92) Forensic Science Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - HB 705-719, 1992. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - HB 721-742, 1992. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - HB 744-755, 1992. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - HB 757-782, 1992. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - HB 785-789, 1992. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - HB 790-802, 1992. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - HB 803-817, 1992. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - HB 819-858, 1992. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - HB 859-873, 1992. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - HB 874-898, 1992. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - HB 899-916, 1992. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - HB 920-956, 1992. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - HB 960-984, 1992. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - HB 986-1008, 1992. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - HB 1011-1028, 1992. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - HB 1032-1055, 1992. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - HB 1060-1083, 1992. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - HB 1090-1119, 1992. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - HB 1123-1139, 1992. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - HB 1141-1170, 1992. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - HB 1172-1187, 1992. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - HB 1188-1198, 1992. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Senate Bills, 1992.
    - SB 1-28, 1992. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - SB 33-59, 1992. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - SB 62-78, 1992. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - SB 80-99, 1992. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - SB 100-101, 1992. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - SB 103-117, 1992. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - SB 120-130, 1992. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - SB 132-149, 1992. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - SB 151-170, 1992. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - SB 174-190, 1992. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - SB 192-195, 1992. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - SB 200-219, 1992. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - SB 221-237, 1992. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - SB 244-264, 1992. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - SB 268-285, 1992. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - SB 291-310, 1992. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - SB 312-346, 1992. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - SB 347-365, 1992. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - SB 366-392, 1992. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - SB 393-435, 1992. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - SB 436-461, 1992. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - SB 462-487, 1992. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - SB 490-507, 1992. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - SB 508-525, 1992. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Amended / Reenrolled Legislation, 1992.
    - HB 30-219, 1992. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - HB 232-388, 1992. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - HB 415-563, 1992. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - HB 564-710, 1992. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - HB 713-756, 1992. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - HB 769-917, 1992. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - HB 919-1001, 1992. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - HB 1023-1077, 1992. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - HB 1115-1197, 1992. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - SB 63-143, 1992. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - SB 156-162, 1992. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - SB 165-225, 1992. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - SB 230-270, 1992. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - SB 315-518, 1992. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - SB 522-523, 1992. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Special Session I, 1992.
    - HB 3001-3002, 1992. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - HB 3003, 1992. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - SB 1501-1503, 1992. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Vetoed Legislation, 1992.
    - HB 59-617, 1992. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - HB 775, 914, 1992. (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - HB 1110, 1992. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - HB 1110, 1992. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - HB 1110, 1992. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - HB 1110, 1992. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - HB 1110, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - HB 1110, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - HB 1110, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - SB 67-361, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - SB 408-494, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - SB 524, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 6)
- General Assembly Legislation, 1993.
  - House of Delegates Bills, 1993.
    - HB 38-562, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - HB 599-1107, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - HB 1131-1209, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - HB 1210-1225, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - HB 1229-1267, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - HB 1269-1285, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - HB 1286-1310, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - HB 1312-1329, 1993. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - HB 1330-1345, 1993. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - HB 1348-1379, 1993. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - HB 1380-1405, 1993. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - HB 1406-1418, 1993. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - HB 1420-1433, 1993. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - HB 1434-1448, 1993. (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - HB 1450-1465, 1993. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - HB 1466-1481, 1993. (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - HB 1484-1498, 1993. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - HB 1503-1522, 1993. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - HB 1528-1551, 1993. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - HB 1553-1562, 1993. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - HB 1563, 1993. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - HB 1564-1573, 1993. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - HB 1576-1591, 1993. (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - HB 1592-1599, 1993. (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - HB 1602-1611, 1993. (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - HB 1615-1634, 1993. (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - HB 1635-1649, 1993. (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - HB 1650-1676, 1993. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - HB 1680-1692, 1993. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - HB 1693-1704, 1993. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - HB 1705-1724, 1993. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - HB 1726-1741, 1993. (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - HB 1744-1761, 1993. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - HB 1766-1784, 1993. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - HB 1786-1800, 1993. (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - HB 1801-1812, 1993. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - HB 1815-1829, 1993. (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - HB 1831-1848, 1993. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - HB 1851-1869, 1993. (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - HB 1871-1886, 1993. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - HB 1888-1908, 1993. (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - HB 1910-1928, 1993. (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - HB 1932-1950, 1993. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - HB 1952-1962, 1993. (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - HB 1966-1990, 1993. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - HB 1999-2018, 1993. (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - HB 2024-2042, 1993. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - HB 2045-2068, 1993. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - HB 2072-2099, 1993. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - HB 2101-2114, 1993. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - HB 2117, 1993. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - HB 2121-2140, 1993. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - HB 2144-2163, 1993. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - HB 2169-2185, 1993. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - HB 2187-2218, 1993. (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - HB 2220-2256, 1993. (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - HB 2257-2271, 1993. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - HB 2273-2286, 1993. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - HB 2307-2321, 1993. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - HB 2326-2352, 1993. (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - HB 2357-2379, 1993. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - HB 2380-2396, 1993. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - HB 2400-2437, 1993. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Senate Bills, 1993.
    - SB 114-362, 1993. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - SB 476-541, 1993. (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - SB 551-575, 1993. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - SB 576-593, 1993. (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - SB 594-609, 1993. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - SB 611-621, 1993. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - SB 623-635, 1993. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - SB 638-646, 1993. (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - SB 649-663, 1993. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - SB 665-682, 1993. (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - SB 683-697, 1993. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - SB 698-710, 1993. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - SB 711-730, 1993. (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - SB 731-747, 1993. (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - SB 750-773, 1993. (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - SB 776-784, 1993. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - SB 786-805, 1993. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - SB 808-837, 1993. (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - SB 843-856, 1993. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - SB 858-872, 1993. (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - SB 873-887, 1993. (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - SB 888-905, 1993. (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - SB 910-925, 1993. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - SB 927-957, 1993. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - SB 959-975, 1993. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - SB 976-999, 1993. (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - SB 1000-1023, 1993. (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - SB 1024-1066, 1993. (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Amended / Reenrolled Legislation, 1993.
    - HB 352-1224, 1993. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - HB 1228-1306, 1993. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - HB 1328-1460, 1993. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - HB 1475-1486, 1993. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - HB 1502-1574, 1993. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - HB 1575-1652, 1993. (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - HB 1678-1758, 1993. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - HB 1763-1827, 1993. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - HB 1845-1903, 1993. (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - HB 1930-1988, 1993. (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - HB 1993-2154, 1993. (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - HB 2167-2282, 1993. (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - HB 2312-2421, 1993. (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - SB 85-536, 1993. (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - SB 547-691, 1993. (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - SB 749-852, 1993. (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - SB 869-906, 1993. (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - SB 908-934, 1993. (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - SB 943-965, 1993. (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - SB 1002-1064, 1993. (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Vetoed Legislation, 1993.
    - HB 593-1614, 1993. (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - HB 1751-2200, 1993. (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - SB 610, 804, 974, 1993. (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - SB 632-1040, 1993. (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Special Session I, 1993.
    - SB 2001-2003, 1993. (Box 71, Folder 3)